Richard J. Neutra Papers
Richard J. Neutra Papers
- Recordings
  - [no title], neutra_rj_118; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - [no title], neutra_rj_119; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - [no title], neutra_rj_121; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - [no title], neutra_rj_126; label says "To Mr. and Mrs. Richard Neutra 2300 Silverlake Blvd"; contents unknown; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - [no title], neutra_rj_128; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
- Writings
  - Essays, A-S, 7 folders (Box 2)
  - Essays, T-Z, 1 folder (Box 3)
  - Notes
    - General, 1953-1966; undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Projects
      - Orange County Court House (Box 3)
        See also Drawings: Original architectural drawings.
      - Tower of Hope (Box 3)
      - VDL House (Box 3)
      - West Pakistan University (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
    - Richard J. Neutra and Associates (Box 3)
    - Richard J. Neutra Foundation (Box 3)
    - Richard J. Neutra Institute (Box 3)
  - Speeches, A-Z, 4 folders (Box 3)